Register of the American Children's Fund Records, 1923-1950
Hoover Institution Archives
- Boy Scouts of America, 1922-1956. (Box No. 26-40.)
  - Subject file
    - Health and Safety Program
      - Report of Crampton, Hoyt, Krueger, 1935-1937 (Folder 2)
      - Subject file
        - Dental health (Folder 3)
        - Field visits (Folder 4)
        - Five Year Program (Folder 5)
        - Plans and future projects, 1935-1938 (Folder 6)
        - Training operations
          - 1936-1937 (Folder 7)
          - 1938-1946 (Folder 8)
    - Health and Safety Service (Box 37.)
      - General (Folder 1)
      - Financial records
        - General (Folder 2)
        - Budget, 1935-1944 (Folder 3)
      - Grant study, 1943-1945 (Folder 4)
      - Report to the American Children's Fund, Special Projects, 1947-1948 (Folder 5)
      - Subject file - Sex education (Folder 6)
    - Health Program
      - General (Folder 7-8)
      - Reports. Treasurer's reports, 1935, 1942 (Folder 9)
      - Subject file
        - Krueger, J. W. Correspondence, notes, reports, 1933-1934 (Folder 10)
        - New Haven Experiment (Box 38., Folder 1-3)
        - Special Medical Advisory Committee. Correspondence and Interim Report, 1938 (Folder 4-6)
    - Infantile paralysis (polio) (Box 39., Folder 1)
    - Inter-racial service (Folder 2)
    - Leadership training course, 1947-1948 (Folder 3)
    - Malaria mosquito (Folder 4)
    - Maui Council, 1943-1945 (Folder 5)
    - Medical examinations
      - General, 1948 (Folder 6)
      - Form (Folder 7)
    - Merit badges (Folder 8)
    - North Shore (Chicago) Council (Folder 9)
    - Oath (Folder 10)
    - Officers and Executive Board (Folder 11)
    - Operation Zero, 1947 January 4-11 (Folder 12)
    - Pediatrics (Folder 13)
    - Phillips, Waite (Folder 14)
    - Phillips Academy (Andover) (Folder 15)
    - Physical fitness (Folder 16)
    - Posters. Correspondence, memoranda, reports relating to poster production, 1948-1949 (Folder 17)
    - Powers, Pliny H. (Folder 18)
    - Pre-Ranger Training Program (Folder 19)
    - Regional Committee, Region Two (Folder 20)
    - Rifle range (Folder 21)
    - Rope ladders (Folder 22)
    - Sea Scouts disaster, 1943 April 26 (Folder 23)
    - Silver Buffalo Award (Folder 24)
    - Social hygiene (Folder 25)
    - Swimming, watersports safety (Folder 26)
    - Training programs (Box 40.)
      - General (Folder 1)
      - Camp leaders and scoutmasters, 1946-1948 (Folder 2-3)
      - Emergency service
        - General (Folder 4)
        - Schiff Scout Reservation (Folder 5)
    - Troop meeting place inspection form (Folder 6)
    - Victory Corps (Folder 7)
- Girl Scouts of America, 1920-1951. (Box No. 40-48.)
  Correspondence, memoranda, reports, financial records, minutes of meetings, printed matter and other materials. Relates to operations of the Boy Scouts of America and the funding received from the American Children's Fund. Arranged alphabetically by physical form and thereunder by subject.
  - Correspondence
    - General, 1919-1929 (Box 40., Folder 8)
    - Barnard, Margaret, 1944-1946 (Folder 9)
    - Bronkenhorst, Anne, 1948 (Box 41., Folder 1)
    - De Blois, Lewis, Mrs., 1939-1947 (Folder 2)
    - Galpin, Perrin, 1940-1948 (Folder 3)
    - Hoover, Lou Henry, 1939 (Folder 4)
    - Janeway, Margaret, 1940-1946 (Folder 5)
    - Lewis, Margaret, 1940-1947 (Folder 6)
    - Rickard, Edgar, 1945 (Folder 7)
    - Rittenhouse, Paul, Mrs., 1940-1950 (Folder 8)
    - Wright, Ralph, Mrs., 1944 (Folder 9)
  - Financial records
    - Appropriations file
      - 1926-1932 (Folder 10)
      - 1932-1935 (Folder 11)
      - 1935-1936 (Box 42., Folder 1)
      - 1936-1938 (Folder 2)
      - 1939-1946 (Folder 3)
    - Expense file, 1944-1945 (Folder 4)
    - Reports. Auditor's reports
      - 1930-1932 (Folder 5)
      - 1933-1936 (Folder 6)
      - 1936-1940 (Folder 7)
    - Subject file (Box 43.)
      - Budget, 1932 (Folder 1)
      - Development Fund
        - 1930-1932 (Folder 2)
        - 1932-1933 (Folder 3)
        - 1933-1934 (Folder 4)
      - Loans to The American Girl magazine, 1927-1929 (Folder 5)
      - Objectives, 1930-1935 (Folder 6)
      - Publication Fund, 1925-1932 (Folder 7)
  - Meetings file. Correspondence, memoranda, reports, studies, and notes
    - General (Folder 8)
    - Arts and Crafts Committee, 1943 (Folder 9)
    - Board of Directors, 1931 March 17-18 (Folder 10)
    - Health and Safety Advisory Committee (Box 44.)
      - 1945 (Folder 1)
      - 1946 (Folder 2)
    - Health and Safety Committee
      - 1939-1940 (Folder 3)
      - 1941 (Folder 4)
      - 1942 (Folder 5)
      - 1943 (Folder 6)
      - 1944 (Folder 7)
      - 1945 (Folder 8)
      - 1946 (Folder 9)
    - National Board, 1942 March 20 (Box 45., Folder 1)
    - Program Committee
      - 1942 (Folder 2)
      - 1943 (Folder 3)
      - 1944 (Folder 4)
  - Printed matter
    - General (Folder 5-7)
    - General (Box 46., Folder 1-3)
    - Girl Scout Leader
      - 1939-1942 (Folder 4)
      - 1943-1948 (Folder 5)
    - Girl Scouts All, 1945 April (Folder 6)
  - Reports (Box 47.)
    - General
      - General
        - 1940-1941 (Folder 1)
        - 1943 (Folder 2)
        - 1944 ("Report on Health and Safety) (Folder 3)
      - Annual reports, 1937, 1939 (Folder 4)
      - President's reports, 1944-1945 (Folder 5)
      - Treasurer's report, 1944 (Folder 6)
    - Health and Safety Project, 1939-1942 (Folder 7)
    - Medical Advisory Committee, 1942-1943 (Folder 8)
    - Program Committee, 1944 (Folder 9)
  - Stationery (Folder 10)
  - Subject file
    - General (Folder 11-12)
    - Adult jobs and defense, 1941 (Box 48., Folder 1)
    - Annual dinner, 1943 March 9 (Folder 2)
    - Brouha Step Test (Folder 3)
    - Camp standards (Folder 4)
    - Clothing Kit Committee (Folder 5)
    - Dental health (Folder 6)
    - Famine Emergency Committee (Folder 7)
    - Girl Scout Leader, 1940 (Folder 8)
    - Good manners book (Folder 9)
    - Health and Safety Committee (Folder 10)
    - Health and Safety Program
      - General (Folder 11)
      - Physically handicapped girl scouts (Folder 12)
    - International conferences, 1949-1950 (Folder 13)
    - Life saving requirements (Folder 14)
    - Membership drives, 1943-1944 (Folder 15)
    - Occupational therapists aides (Folder 16)
    - Pediatrics (Folder 17)
    - Physical Training Program of the Women's Army Corps, 1943 (Folder 18)
    - Questionnaires, 1940-1942 (Folder 19)
    - Richard Memorial Award (Folder 20)
    - Vita-Min-Go (Folder 21)